# LEX LING

# EDUCATION

09/2014 - 05/2018 **NEW YORK UNIVERSITY** (3.816/4.0) New York, NY

Gallatin School of Individualized Study

Individualized Major focused on design, art history, visual culture, and marketing

Minor: Business of Entertainment, Media, and

Technology (Stern School of Business)

Design I & II // Contemporary Visual Culture and the Politics COURSES

of Images // Entertainment & Media Industries // Media,

Technology, and Society // Creative Computing

**ACTIVITIES** Founder and President of Gallazine

**Emerging Leader Award** 

Dean's List

08/2016 - 12/2016 **NEW YORK UNIVERSITY SHANGHAI** (4.0/4.0)

Shanghai, China Study Abroad: General Curriculum and

Interactive Media Arts

Communications Lab // Projects in Western and Chinese **COURSES** 

Methods of Art // Chinese II

#### EXPERIENCE

01/2017 - Present New York, NY

#### AMINO APPS // Design Intern

// Design and illustrate app icons, mobile assets, and iOS and Android screenshots for app stores

// Social media rebrand of Instagram and Twitter, design ad campaigns, make graphics and animations for social media, mockup mobile UI designs

// "Amino VIP" branding, assist with Amino style guide, and create cohesive image across all Amino platforms

// Reach out to artists to feature fan content on Amino

02/2016 - 06/2016 New York, NY

# **VISIT.ORG** // Visual Editor Intern

// Curate, edit, and upload images to WordPress for organization pages, organize images and design promotional presentations

09/2015 - 11/2015 New York, NY

#### THE HOLE // Gallery and Operations Intern

// Open and close gallery, greet visitors, install and deinstall exhibitions, handle art, design exhibit postcards

02/2015 - 06/2015 New York, NY

#### SCHOLASTIC // Art Dept Admin Assistant

// Invoice and record-keeping, contract editing, sample warehouse ordering

// Image and photo research, file conversion, assemble prototypes, create "child-like" drawings and handwriting for products

07/2013 - 08/2013 New York, NY

## THE MET // Education and Digital Media Intern

// Edit thumbnail images for new audio guides // Verify, organize, and tabulate content from 10+ audio guides with 100+ audio guide tour stops

// Create and lead group gallery tour and discussion

**EMAIL:** <u>aswling@nyu.edu</u> **PHONE:** (908) 399-5353 LOCATION: NY // NJ

## PROFILE

Hi! I'm Alex. I'm currently a senior at NYU's Gallatin School of Individualized Study where I'm pursuing an individualized major concentrating in design, art history, and marketing, specifically the ways to best visually communicate ideas and narratives. I'm also minoring in BEMT at NYU's Stern School of Business. I have professional experience in design, visual curation, and making creative content. In my free time, I'm usually found drawing comics and working on my UI/UX skills.

WEBSITE LINKEDIN **PORTFOLIO GITHUB INSTAGRAM**  aswling.com /alexandraling @alexswling /aswling @aswling

#### **SKILLS**

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign Premiere Audacity HTML/CSS JavaScript InVision Photography PaintTool SAL



## FAVE PROJECTS

<u>Skin Deep</u> (2016)

Amino Instagram Rebrand (2017)

FEED Magazine (2017)

Through the Bund (2016)

Zàijiàn (2016)

Homecoming (2017)

Of Mice and Men (2017)